Guide to the New Dimensions Media records M1577
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Accession 2008-144
  - Sub-Series 7: Photographs, 7
    - "M" letter guests: Steve Morse Band; unidentified black and white of South Asian man (Box 164, Folder 19)
    - Naess, Arne (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Nair, Keshavan (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Naisbitt, John and Patricia Aburdene (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Naparstek, Belleruth (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Napier, Nance (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Native Wisdom Conference, Eugene Oregon, March 1992 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Needleman, Jacob (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Negroponte, Nicholas (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Nemeth, Maria (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Newman, Nell (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Nisker, Wes "Scoop" (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Norberg-Hodge, Helena (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Norris, Kathleen (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Nozick, Robert (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Nuland, Sherwin (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Null, Gary (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - "N" letter guests: Holly Near, Michael Nagler, Claudio Naranjo, Vicki Noble, Pam Colorado, Edne Landes, Mary Jones, Navajo Elders (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - O'Connor, John and Joan Felt (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Odent, Michel (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Orloff, Judith (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - O'Leary, Brian (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - O'Mara, Peggy (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - O'Donohue, John (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Ormann, Susie (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Ornish, Dean and Rachel Naomi Remen (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - O'Regan, Brendan (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Orsborn, Carol (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Oyle, Susan (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Palmer, Helen (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Parenti, Michael (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Parry, Danaan (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Pasick, Rob and Marilyn Mason (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Patent, Arnold (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Paul, Margaret and Jordan Paul (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Paul, Russill and Fr. Bede Griffiths (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Peat, David (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Peacemaking Conference: Luciano Pecsi, Sasha Killner-Rogers (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Pearce, Joseph Chilton (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Pearson, Carol (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Peavey, Fran and Charlie Varon (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Perez Esquivel, Adolfo (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Pert, Candace (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Peterson, Brenda (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Phillips, Christopher (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Phillips, Mark (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Phillips, Michael (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Phipps, Carter (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Pierrakos, John and Siegmar Gerken (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Pike, Diane Kenedy and Arleen Lorrance (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Plant, Chris and Judith Plant (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Pope, Carl (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Porter, Angela and Emily Hooker (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Portland event: Fundraiser September 1995: Gary Zukav, LInda Zukav, Marge Abbott, Sherman Severin, Mary Manin Morrissey, Linda Fracis Jean Houston, Nicki Scully, Sara Halprin, Amit Goswami (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Poyacnik, Mike (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Prager, Judith (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Prather, Hugh and Gayle Prather (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Prechtel, Martin (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Prentice, Beatriz (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Pribram, Karl and Mrs. Pribram (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Pritchard, Evan (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Purce, Jill (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Radha, Swami (Box 166, Folder 14)
    - Radir, Dean (Box 166, Folder 14)
    - Ram Dass (Box 166, Folder 14)
      One color slide
    - Raging Grannies (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Randour, Mary Lou (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Ray, Michael (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Ray, Sondra (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Rebillot, Paul (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Rechstaffen, Stephen (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Reder, Alan (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Redfield, Salle Merrill and James Redfield (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Reeve, Susyn (Box 166, Folder 18)
    - Remen, Rachel (Box 166, Folder 18)
    - Reich, Charles (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Reinhold, Barbard B. (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Reichert, Josh (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Reynolds, David (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Rheingold, Howard (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Ricard, Matthew and Jean Francois, Dalai Lama (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Richards, Dick (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Richards, Mary (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Rico, Gabriele (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Roads, Michael (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Robbins, John (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Robert, Karl-Henrik (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, Bernadette (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Roberts, Wendy Hunter (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Robin, Vicki and Joe Dominguez (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Roddick, Anita (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Rosen, Gerald (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Rosen, Marion (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Rosenberg, Marshall and Valentina Rosenberg (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Roshi, Robert Aitken (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Ross, Ruth (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Roszak, Theodore (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Roth, Gabrielle (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Roth, Geneen (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Rowell, Galen (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Rothschild, Joel (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Rubenfeld, IIana and Judy Collins (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Rubik, Beverly (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Ruiz, Don Miguel (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Russell, Peter (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Ryerson, Kevin (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - "R" letter guests: Richard Romero, Deborah Rozman, Jonas Robertson, and photocopy of Dick and Jeanne Roy, Sogyal Rinpoche (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor holding the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, November 1949, Lake Success, N.Y. (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Sahtouris, Elisabet (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Sale, Kirkpatrick (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Salzberg, Sharon (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Satir, Virginia (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Schachter, Reb Zalmon and Eve Ilsen (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Schaef, Anne Wilson (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Schieber, Barry (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Schlitiz, Marilyn and Tom Hurley, Elizabeth Targ (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Schmaltz, David (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Schmookler, Andrew (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Schneider, Meir (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Schneider, Richard (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Schreiber, Jon and Angela Porter, Dennise Berenzowsky (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Schroder-Sheker, Therese (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Schutz, Will (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Carter-Scott, Cherie (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Schwartz, Gary (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Schwartz, Jack (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Schwartz, Tony (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Scully, Nicki (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Seed, John (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Segal, Jeanne (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Segal Joseph and Nathan Segal (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Seitz, Ron (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Sessions, George and Arne Naess (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Shaffer, Carolyn and Kristin Anundsen (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Sharif, Abdullah (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Sheldrake Rupert (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Sherman, Jeremy and Lois Barber (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Shepard, Paul (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Shepherd, Linda Jean (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Sher, Barbara (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Sherman, Gordon (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Shlain, Leonard (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Shuddhananda (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Sidhwa, Bapsi (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Siegel, Bernie (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Silverstein, Olga (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Simon, Stephen (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Simonton, Carl (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Simonton, Stephanie (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Sinetar, Marsha (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Singer, June (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Singh, Tara (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Sivaraksa, Sulak (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Skolimowski, Henryk and Joan Skolimowski (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Skutch, Robert (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Sluyter, Dean (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Small, Jacqueline and Jeremiah Abrams (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Helene and Andrew Weil (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Huston (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Smoley, Richard (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Snyder, Gary (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Sogyal, Rinpoche (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Solnit, Rebecca (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Soloman, Norman (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Some, Malidoma and Sobonfu Some (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Sommer, Mark and Richard Strozzi Heckler (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Speeth, Kathleen (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Spock, Benjamin and Mary Morgan (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Spretnak, Charlene (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Spong, Bishop John (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - St. Andrews, Barbara Rev. and Andrew Weil (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - Stamford, Bryant (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - Starcke, Walter (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - Starhawk (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - Marabai, Starr (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - Steindl-Rast, Brother David and Fritjof Capra, Daniel Uvanovic, Joshua Nicholson (Box 168, Folder 18)
    - Steinem, Gloria (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Sterns, Ann Kaiser (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Stewart, William (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Stone, Hal and Sidra Stone (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Stone, Merlin (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Storm, Hyemeyohsts (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Streiber, Whitley (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Sudo, Philip Toshio (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Sun, Patricia (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Surya Das (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Suzuki, David (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Swigart, Rob (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Swimme, Brian and Thomas Berry (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - S.P.A.C.E.: Anna Araiza, Andrew Kircher, Cy PLatt, David Lincoln, Christine Hamilton, Rick Hamilton (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - "S" letter guests: Jamie Sams, Richard Schiffman (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Tae Yun Kim (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Tai Situ Rinpoche (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Takaki Ron (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Talbot, Michael (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - alen, Bill and Lorri Holt (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Tannan, Deborah (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Tarlows, Micaela and Philip Tarlows (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Tarnas, Richard (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Tart, Charles and Arthur Hastings (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Taylor, C. Holland (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Taylor, Eugene (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Taylor, Susan and Khephra Burns (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Taylor, Terry Lynn (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Teasdale, Bro. Wayne and Jim Williams (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Teish, Luisah (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Tellington-Jones, Linda (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - Templeton, Sir John (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - Terkel, Studs and John Sayles (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - Theobald, Robert (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - Thich Nhat Hanh (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - Thomas, Guboo Ted (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Thompkins, Doug (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Thompson, Wm. Irwin (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Thorne, David (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Thurman, Robert (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Timms, Moira (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Timpanelli, Gioia (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Tiwari, Maya (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Tiso, Father (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Tolle, Eckart (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Tompkins, Peter (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Trask, Mililani (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Travel Program: Conrad Levasseur, Carole Angermeier (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Tsering, Lama (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Tudge, Colin (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Tulku, Thondup (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Tuttle, Will (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Twist, Lynn: Lynn Twist Event, 1995: Jean Houston, Charles Garfield, LaUna Huffines, Austin Marx, Jim Fadiman, John Gillespie, Pat Barrentine (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Twotrees, Kaylynn Sullivan (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Ullman, Dana (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Umoja, Mbali (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Uttal, Jai (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Utne, Nina and Jay Walljasper (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Vallee, Jacques (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Van Derhoff, Jean (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Van der Post, Sir Laurens (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Van der Ryn, Sim (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Van Dusen, Wilson (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Vanzant, Iyanla (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Varian, Heidi (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Vasconcellos, John (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Vaughan, Frances (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Vaughan-Lee, Llewellyn (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Vazquez, Francisco (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Verny, Thomas (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Vijali (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Villasana-Ruiz, Rosario (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Vinayakram, T. H. "Vikku" and Zakir Hussain (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Virtue, Doreen (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Vogel, Karen (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Vogel, Marcel (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Volk, Tyler (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Vyfhuis, Che (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Alice Walker and Joan Miura (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Walker, Cathy Hawk and Michael Walker, Gary Hawk (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Walker, Rebecca (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Wallace, Nancy (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Walsch, Neale Donald (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Walsh, Roger (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Walstrom, Mark (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Wasserman, Harvey (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Watts, Steven (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Weatherford, Jack (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Weber, Renee (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Weed, Susun (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Weil, Andrew and Rev. Barbara St. Andrews, Barbara Bernie, Helene Smith (Box 171, Folder 2)
      One negative
    - Weiner, David (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Weiner, Jan (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Weiss, Brian (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Weissberg, Michael (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Welch, Brian (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Wells, Peter (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Welwood, John (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Wennstrom, Jerry and Marilyn Strong (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Wheatley, Meg and Myron Kellner-Rogers (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - White, Lavina (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Whiteley, Richard (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Whyte, David (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Betty (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Paul (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Terry Tempest (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Williamson, Marianne (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Colin (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, John Oliver (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Winn, Marie (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Winter, Paul and Spencer Brewer (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Wisdom Circles (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Witherspoon, Bill and Dan Drasin, Jeff Wessman, Ralph Steiner (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Wolf, Fred Alan (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Wolf, LInda and K. Wind Hughes (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Wolf-Hardin, Jesse (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Wolkstein, Diane (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Wolter, Dwight Lee (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Woodman, Marion (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Worrall, Olga (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - "W" letter guests (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Young, Jonathan and David Kudler (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Young, Shinzen (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Young-Sowers, Meredith (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Youth interviews, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Yunnus, Mohamed (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Ywahoo, Dhyani (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Zeller, David (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Zinn, Howard (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Zohar, Danah (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Zukav, Gary (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Zweig, Connie and Jeremiah Abrams (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Various guests: Dona Andrea, Tai Situpa, Babatunde Olatunji, Mickey Hart, Sikiru Adeoju, Petra Kelly and husband, Ann Niehaus Duane Elgin, John Sheck Yee, Br. Jack Graham, Cynthia Palmer, Michael Horowitz, Ellen Purser, Subhuti Dharmananada, George Weissman, Mel Krantzler, Richard Marsh, Ru, Ram Dass, Jack Schwartz, Patricia Sun, Peters and Austin (Box 171, Folder 18)
    - Various guests, unidentified (Box 171, Folder 19)
      2 negatives